If you have read language in elementary school and have at least E on that subject, you can count on it as their 17th rating.
At high school.se there is a credit calculator, how smoothly?
I know that many can be worried about the credit value, can you see somewhere what it has looked like before?
Yes you can through your high school admission.
There you can see statistics from previous years and get a picture of what the search pressure looked like and what credit value may be required.
If you do not know if you will be qualified or not to a national high school program, what is important to consider then?
If you are unauthorized for the national high school programs, there are four different introductory programs that you can apply for.
If you are at risk of not being qualified, it is important that you have any of the options from the introductory programs in your application.
What is meant by introductory programs?
On the introductory programs, all students have an individual study plan.
With the aim of either being eligible for a national high school program or with the goal of being able to enter the labor market.
What suits you best and what you are qualified for can look very different depending on what subjects and how many subjects you lack grades from elementary school.
To know more about the alternatives you can talk to the study and the career counselor at your school.
But you can also read more about them in articles here at high school.se
Thank you so much Melina for wanting to be here again.
Thanks for coming here!
I've got a lot of good info!